const qBank = [
  {
    question:
      "No one cares about your birthday.",
    answers: ["Angela Martin","Stanley Hudson","Michael Scott","Pam Beesly"],
    correct: "Angela Martin",
    questionId: "1"
  },
    {
    question:
      "I talk a lot, so I’ve learned to tune myself out.",
    answers: ["Ryan Howard","Kelly Kapoor","Kevin Malone","Oscar Martinez"],
    correct: "Kelly Kapoor",
    questionId: "2"
  },
    {
    question:
      "If I don’t have some cake soon, I might die.",
    answers: ["Andy Bernard","Dwight Schrute","Angela Martin","Stanley Hudson"],
    correct: "Stanley Hudson",
    questionId: "3"
  },
    {
    question:
      "I am Beyoncé always.",
    answers: ["Stanley Hudson","Michael Scott","Pam Beesly","Andy Bernard"],
    correct: "Michael Scott",
    questionId: "4"
  },
    {
    question:
      "I don't care what they say about me. I just want to eat.",
    answers: ["Kevin Malone","Oscar Martinez","Michael Scott","Pam Beesly"],
    correct: "Pam Beesly",
    questionId: "5"
  },
    {
    question:
      "Sorry I annoyed you with my friendship.",
    answers: ["Andy Bernard","Dwight Schrute","Jim Halpert","Robert California"],
    correct: "Andy Bernard",
    questionId: "6"
  },
    {
    question:
      "I’m an early bird and I’m a night owl so I’m wise and I have worms.",
    answers: ["Michael Scott","Andy Bernard","Dwight Schrute","Creed Bratton"],
    correct: "Michael Scott",
    questionId: "7"
  },
    {
    question:
      "Bread is the paper of the food industry. You write your sandwich on it.",
    answers: ["Andy Bernard","Dwight Schrute","Jim Halpert","Creed Bratton"],
    correct: "Dwight Schrute",
    questionId: "8"
  },
    {
    question:
      "Do I regret this? No, I believe his tissue has made me stronger. I now have the strength of a grown man and a little baby.",
    answers: ["Andy Bernard","Dwight Schrute","Jim Halpert","Robert California",],
    correct: "Dwight Schrute",
    questionId: "9"
  },
    {
    question:
      "I am about to do something very bold in this job that I’ve never done before: try.",
    answers: ["Jim Halpert","Robert California","Ryan Howard","Kelly Kapoor"],
    correct: "Jim Halpert",
    questionId: "10"
  },
    {
    question:
      "From time to time I send Dwight faxes. From himself. From the future.",
    answers: ["Jim Halpert","Robert California","Ryan Howard","Pam Beesly"],
    correct: "Jim Halpert",
    questionId: "11"
  },
    {
    question:
      "Sold out!? That has never happened in the history of jinx!",
    answers: ["Ryan Howard","Pam Beesly","Kevin Malone","Kelly Kapoor"],
    correct: "Pam Beesly",
    questionId: "12"
  },
    {
    question:
      "Do I look like someone who would waste my own time?",
    answers: ["Robert California","Ryan Howard","Kelly Kapoor","Angela Martin"],
    correct: "Robert California",
    questionId: "13"
  },
    {
    question:
      "You can't have a favorite Iron Chef. It depends entirely on the secret ingredient.",
    answers: ["Jim Halpert","Robert California","Andy Bernard","Dwight Schrute"],
    correct: "Robert California",
    questionId: "14"
  },
    {
    question:
      "I know a few things about love. Horrible, terrible, awful, awful things.",
    answers: ["Michael Scott","Andy Bernard","Dwight Schrute","Ryan Howard"],
    correct: "Andy Bernard",
    questionId: "15"
  },
    {
    question:
      "I'm not saying I had a meteoric rise, but I did.",
    answers: ["Phyllis Lapin-Vance","Creed Bratton","Meredith Palmer","Ryan Howard"],
    correct: "Ryan Howard",
    questionId: "16"
  },
    {
    question:
      "You can't let a girl feel good about herself. It will backfire on you.",
    answers: ["Michael Scott","Creed Bratton","Andy Bernard","Ryan Howard"],
    correct: "Andy Bernard",
    questionId: "17"
  },
    {
    question:
      "I mean, who says exactly what they're thinking? What kind of game is that?",
    answers: ["Angela Martin","Stanley Hudson","Kelly Kapoor","Michael Scott"],
    correct: "Kelly Kapoor",
    questionId: "18"
  },
    {
    question:
      "Whenever I try to make a taco, I get too excited and crush it.",
    answers: ["Andy Bernard","Dwight Schrute","Kevin Malone","Stanley Hudson"],
    correct: "Kevin Malone",
    questionId: "19"
  },
    {
    question:
      "I consider myself a good person, but I'm gonna try to make him cry.",
    answers: ["Creed Bratton","Meredith Palmer","Kevin Malone","Oscar Martinez"],
    correct: "Oscar Martinez",
    questionId: "20"
  },
    {
    question:
      "I love catching people in the act. That's why I always whip open doors.",
    answers: ["Andy Bernard","Dwight Schrute","Ryan Howard","Kelly Kapoor"],
    correct: "Dwight Schrute",
    questionId: "21"
  },
    {
    question:
      "The man is wearing sandals. I don’t need to see Oscar’s toes at work.",
    answers: ["Angela Martin","Stanley Hudson","Phyllis Lapin-Vance","Creed Bratton"],
    correct: "Angela Martin",
    questionId: "22"
  },
    {
    question:
      "I think for it to be blackmail, it would have to be a formal letter.",
    answers: ["Michael Scott","Pam Beesly","Angela Martin","Phyllis Lapin-Vance"],
    correct: "Phyllis Lapin-Vance",
    questionId: "23"
  },
    {
    question:
      "You’re ugly and I know it for a fact ’cause I got the evidence right there.",
    answers: ["Michael Scott","Pam Beesly","Angela Martin","Kelly Kapoor"],
    correct: "Kelly Kapoor",
    questionId: "24"
  },
    {
    question:
      "Oh, you’re paying way too much for worms. Who’s your worm guy?",
    answers: ["Michael Scott","Creed Bratton","Oscar Martinez","Phyllis Lapin-Vance"],
    correct: "Creed Bratton",
    questionId: "25"
  },
    {
    question:
      "Ryan Howard is a junior sales associate at a mid-range paper supply firm.’ That’ll show ’em.",
    answers: ["Michael Scott","Creed Bratton","Angela Martin","Ryan Howard"],
    correct: "Ryan Howard",
    questionId: "26"
  },
    {
    question:
      "Who is Justice Beaver?",
    answers: ["Andy Bernard","Dwight Schrute","Michael Scott","Creed Bratton"],
    correct: "Dwight Schrute",
    questionId: "27"
  },
    {
    question:
      "Tell him to call me ASAP as possible.",
    answers: ["Andy Bernard","Dwight Schrute","Michael Scott","Creed Bratton"],
    correct: "Michael Scott",
    questionId: "28"
  },
    {
    question:
      "I already won the lottery. I was born in the US of A, baby. And as backup, I have a Swiss passport",
    answers: ["Andy Bernard","Stanley Hudson","Ryan Howard","Creed Bratton"],
    correct: "Creed Bratton",
    questionId: "29"
  },
    {
    question:
      "Tell ya one thing, I’m not gonna be a good mom tonight.",
    answers: ["Meredith Palmer","Pam Beesly","Phyllis Lapin-Vance","Kelly Kapoor"],
    correct: "Meredith Palmer",
    questionId: "30"
  },
    {
    question:
      "Rit-dit-dit-do-doo!",
    answers: ["Ryan Howard","Creed Bratton","Andy Bernard","Michael Scott"],
    correct: "Andy Bernard",
    questionId: "31"
  },
    {
    question:
      "Not bad for a day in the life of a dog food company.",
    answers: ["Michael Scott","Ryan Howard","Creed Bratton","Kevin Malone"],
    correct: "Creed Bratton",
    questionId: "32"
  },
    {
    question:
      "I know it's illegal in Pennsylvania, but it's for charity",
    answers: ["Michael Scott","Dwight Schrute","Creed Bratton","Kevin Malone"], 
    correct: "Michael Scott",
    questionId: "33"
  },
    {
    question:
      "I dont believe you, continue.",
    answers: ["Michael Scott","Ryan Howard","Dwight Schrute","Kelly Kapoor"],
    correct: "Dwight Schrute",
    questionId: "34"
  },
    {
    question:
      "I hate so much about the way you choose to be.",
    answers: ["Dwight Schrute","Robert California","Michael Scott","Meredith Palmer"],
    correct: "Michael Scott",
    questionId: "35"
  },
    {
    question:
      "False. I do not miss him.",
    answers: ["Jim Halpert","Robert California","Dwight Schrute","Ryan Howard"],
    correct: "Dwight Schrute",
    questionId: "36"
  },
    {
    question:
      "I haven't been on a first date in 9 years.",
    answers: ["Michael Scott","Phyllis Lapin-Vance","Pam Beesly","Meredith Palmer"],
    correct: "Pam Beesly",
    questionId: "37"
  },
    {
    question:
      "You should order the most expensive item on the menu so he knows you're worth it.",
    answers: ["Michael Scott","Angela Martin","Phyllis Lapin-Vance","Dwight Schrute"],
    correct: "Phyllis Lapin-Vance",
    questionId: "38"
  },
    {
    question:
      "Reject a woman and she will never let it go, it's one of the many defects of their kind.",
    answers: ["Stanley Hudson","Robert California","Michael Scott","Dwight Schrute"],
    correct: "Dwight Schrute",
    questionId: "39"
  },
    {
    question:
      "This isn't your grandmothers christmas party",
    answers: ["Michael Scott","Robert California","Phyllis Lapin-Vance","Pam Beesly"],
    correct: "Phyllis Lapin-Vance",
    questionId: "40"
  },
]; 

export default (n = 5) =>
  Promise.resolve(qBank.sort(() => 0.5 - Math.random()).slice(0, n));
